One sector which has been in the news a bit since this morning is the
insurance sector.
After the LIC numbers came out, we saw that
not only LIC but also HDFC Life, SBI Life,
all the stocks are in the market.
In the second half, the focus has shifted and the
action has shifted a bit towards the general insurance
companies. ICICI Lombard will
come on your screen. New India Assurance will
come on your screen. Both have
seen buying with good volumes.
ICICI Lombard is
around 3.5 on your screen. New India Assurance is
also showing a similar move and is strong. And
after a long time, such a move has been seen. There is
a very interesting development behind this move.
Gold Digital
Tech Insurance Company, which operates in such a space, is
preparing for listing. Let's
check this sector closely.
Yash, after a long time, action is being seen in the general insurance space.
Absolutely Harshada, the
way you explained the sector's in-between
companies, a similar atmosphere
seems to be developing. We had
reported on Saturday that Go Digital, which is a
fact-backed company, is going to file its IP and
DRHP.  It is in the process
and that IP and DRHP has been filed with SEBI today. The
entire IPO of
Goodgetic General Insurance Company is of a very
big size. There will be an
IPO fund raising of approximately Rs 5000 crore, out of which Rs 1250
crore will be fresh, which means
that Rs 1250 crore will come into the company and Rs 3750
crore are selling shareholders, they will participate
through this IPO. The valuation is
very important.
Around 15% equity will be diluted in this IPO,
which will be diluted to raise the value of Rs 5000 crore.
This company,
which is God is IT Insurance, is
valued at Rs 30 to 35 thousand crore. Currently, compare
this valuation with two listed
companies, which are New India Assurance
and ICICI Lombard. The
market cap of ICICI Lombard is around Rs 62000
crore. What is the market cap of New India Assurance? Rs
14000 crore. Currently, the
valuation of Go Digital  The
IPO valuation is expected to be ₹30,000-35,000
crore. The first move after this story came
in New India Shares, which saw a massive
spike. This is because if it gets
listed and is valued at ₹30,000-35,000 crore, as
our sources are
telling us, then New India Assurance will become the
cheapest general insurance company. For
those looking to play in the general insurance
sector, it will be
considered the cheapest entry in the market. This is why
New India Assurance saw such a move,
which was
also seen coming in ICICI Lombard. This is an important
movement. This IPO is a big one. After almost five
years, a new general insurance company is
planning its IPO. The last time this happened was
in 2017 when New India Assurance and
ICICI Lombard were listed. And you are
directly talking about 2022 when Digital Insurance is
planning its IPO. In fact, you
mentioned Prem Vats and Fifex as big companies in the beginning.
How did you forget
Virat Kohli, who is a brand
investor?  He is also there in the company but the
important thing is that there is only one promoter of
goodidge it infotech, he is only the selling share
holder, neither Prem Vats's name is
among the selling shareholders nor any other selling share
holders, Prem will
remain associated with the players, Prem is not good,
in time he has again stated his conviction
in the financial services sector of India
and this is a validation of why he
wants to remain with this company,
interesting development and on the basis of this news,
today New India Sharyas and
ICICI Lombard have also gone, thank you for the
update,
giving details or stem related to insurance and
after many years, in fact after five years,
action will start, Viru, in the EPPU space, for general
insurance,
a cheque should be taken on both New India Sharyas and above,
Shrikant, tell me,
we have discussed ICICI Lombard stock a lot recently,
but the
re-rating expected in New India Sharyas is at least
visible in the market today, on the basis of this
development, should a deal be made, the
stock has fallen by 5%,
sorry my  There is no rate coming near right now, the
internet has become somewhat soft here, till then
what would be the advice of respected sir, which is the better
trade between New India and ICICI Lombard,
so here also a short term breakout has been seen from 4, it
is reverse, you
can expect that you will see prices up to 98 here, so
keep a stop at 89,
but
Iciciment has given the stock and I want a very good breakout, the
breakout is looking very clear
and now the stock is ready to break it, there
is a high possibility that the
stock will update and go towards 1350,
so definitely buy here right now, you
can stop at 1255, a target of 1350 can be
seen in ICICI Lombard,
Sharmila, how much are you looking at the
sector, we all know that
it is good, that is a big story,
but
how much rating can the
entire sector get due to the IPO